quigo.com 2005-04-04

# Quigo Technologies, Inc. - Content-Targeted Ad Serving and Search Engine Marketing Solutions

Quigo Technologies, Inc. places the utmost importance on the privacy of our clients and their businesses. Below are a few common questions and policies regarding privacy and security that we strictly adhere to. If you have any questions, comments or concerns, please do not hesitate to contact us at [support@quigo.com](mailto:support@quigo.com).

### What information does Quigo collect?

We collect and store the information you provide us through your online account. As our partners are aware, our services can involve periodic crawls of their sites, to maintain relevancy, current data, etc. All information collected, including information collected directly from the performance of your account is securely stored and if shared, it only shared on an aggregate basis. Unless otherwise required by law, personally identifiable information is never shared. Quigo notes and saves information such as time of day, browser type and language, and IP address with each query, That information is used to verify our records and to provide more relevant services for users.

### What does Quigo do with my personal information?

We use your personal information solely for the purpose of running your account and communicating account information to you. We would never sell your information and never give it away unless required to by a court of law.

### How secure is my account information?

Quigo is committed to ensure the safety and confidentiality of the information you provide to us. Quigo uses industry-standard SSL (security socket layer) technology to protect every interaction you have with us. This protects your personal information.

### What is a cookie?

A cookie is a piece of data placed on your computer when you visit a Website that identifies you as a unique user. Cookies are very prevalent throughout the Internet. Most users have many cookies on their machine and don't even know it.

### What is Quigo's cookie policy?

Currently, Quigo does not cookie our users or visitors as a regular course of our business. However, we may from time to time cookie visitors in order to gather data. We may use cookies to improve the quality of our service and to understand our user base more. Quigo does this by storing user preferences in cookies and by tracking user trends and patterns of how people use the services. Quigo will not disclose its cookies to third parties nor will we expose any personally identifiable information except as required by a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. This should not affect your use of Quigo. Be aware, however, that some parts of the Internet may not function properly if you refuse cookies.

### Our Partners

The sites displayed as content-targeted listings or linked to by Quigo are provided by third parties. Quigo has no direct control over these sites or companies. All of our partners are subject to our Terms of Service and are not to engage in unlawful activity; however Quigo is not responsible in the event that a partner chooses to violate this policy. Further, these companies and sites may have their own privacy policies and may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Quigo makes no representations or warranties about their practices. You should review the privacy policies of these third party partner sites.

### With Whom Does Quigo Share Information?

Quigo does not share information that is of a personally identifiable nature. We consider that information for use with your particular account only. However, we may from time to time share aggregate information about our users. Again, we will not share personally identifiable information with any third party without your express consent. For example, we may disclose the blended average CPC rate or click through rate, but we will never specify that "company A" had a Y click through rate. Notwithstanding the foregoing, however, in the event we are required by law or in a legal proceeding to provide personally identifiable information, we will do so in order to comply with any valid legal process. Examples include but are not limited to search warrants, subpoenas, statutes, or court orders.

### Your consent and changes to the Privacy Policy

By using any of the Quigo services and our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this policy and to our Terms of Service. Quigo may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

### Questions?

Feel free to contact us any time and we'll answer any additional questions you may have. Our email address is [support@quigo.com](mailto:support@quigo.com).
